mp4point.com 2010-02-27

# Download FREE MP4 Video Movie for PSP, iPod, Mobile and more!

##  [MP4Point.com Privacy Policy](http://www.mp4point.com/privacy-policy/ "Permanent Link to MP4Point.com Privacy Policy")

At MP4Point.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by MP4Point.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, MP4Point.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

MP4Point.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

**MP4Point.com**

MP4Point.com will from time to time review and revise this privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this website. MP4Point.com has the right to change our privacy practices without prior notice. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email.
